{"sid": "JXGRVACOSH5M_main", "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 2225759, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 2225759, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 2232037]], "time_left_end": "294", "answered_time": 2232037, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "294", "question_time_start": 2232037, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["calc_8", 2244428], ["calc_2", 2245128], ["calc_+", 2245966], ["calc_8", 2246739], ["calc_8", 2246868], ["calc_=", 2247635], ["submit", 2251673]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "275", "answered_time": 2251673, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "275", "question_time_start": 2251673, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["calc_4", 2257339], ["calc_7", 2257962], ["calc_+", 2258895], ["calc_2", 2259579], ["calc_8", 2260120], ["calc_=", 2260789], ["submit", 2264111]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "262", "answered_time": 2264111, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "262", "question_time_start": 2264111, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 2274106]], "time_left_end": "252", "answered_time": 2274106, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "252", "question_time_start": 2274107, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 2278466]], "time_left_end": "248", "answered_time": 2278466, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "248", "question_time_start": 2278466, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["submit", 2290036]], "time_left_end": "236", "answered_time": 2290036, "user_answer": "802", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "236", "question_time_start": 2290036, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 2296552]], "time_left_end": "230", "answered_time": 2296552, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "230", "question_time_start": 2296553, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 2311946]], "time_left_end": "214", "answered_time": 2311946, "user_answer": "103", "user_correct": "False", "score": "6"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "214", "question_time_start": 2311946, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 2338019]], "time_left_end": "188", "answered_time": 2338019, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "188", "question_time_start": 2338020, "question": "7+8+23", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 2341764]], "time_left_end": "184", "answered_time": 2341764, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 2341764, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "184", "question_time_start": 2341764, "question": "6+3+59", "correct_answer": 68, "events": [["submit", 2345296]], "time_left_end": "181", "answered_time": 2345296, "user_answer": "68", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "181", "question_time_start": 2345296, "question": "8+84+24", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 2354205]], "time_left_end": "172", "answered_time": 2354205, "user_answer": "116", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "172", "question_time_start": 2354205, "question": "39+87", "correct_answer": 126, "events": [["submit", 2365163]], "time_left_end": "161", "answered_time": 2365163, "user_answer": "126", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "161", "question_time_start": 2365163, "question": "9+8+8+67", "correct_answer": 92, "events": [["submit", 2381386]], "time_left_end": "145", "answered_time": 2381386, "user_answer": "92", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "145", "question_time_start": 2381386, "question": "79+79", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 2385997]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 2385997, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 2385997, "question": "4+3+3+66", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 2391317]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 2391317, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 2391317, "question": "6+68+86", "correct_answer": 160, "events": [["submit", 2404603]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 2404603, "user_answer": "160", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 2404603, "question": "97+597", "correct_answer": 694, "events": [["submit", 2414742]], "time_left_end": "112", "answered_time": 2414742, "user_answer": "694", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "112", "question_time_start": 2414742, "question": "3+8+7+46", "correct_answer": 64, "events": [["submit", 2424488]], "time_left_end": "102", "answered_time": 2424488, "user_answer": "64", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "102", "question_time_start": 2424488, "question": "8+9+18", "correct_answer": 35, "events": [["submit", 2434923]], "time_left_end": "91", "answered_time": 2434923, "user_answer": "35", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 2434923, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "91", "question_time_start": 2434923, "question": "7+4+6+87", "correct_answer": 104, "events": [["submit", 2442931]], "time_left_end": "83", "answered_time": 2442931, "user_answer": "104", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "83", "question_time_start": 2442931, "question": "4+7+6+66", "correct_answer": 83, "events": [["submit", 2452402]], "time_left_end": "74", "answered_time": 2452402, "user_answer": "83", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "74", "question_time_start": 2452403, "question": "23+39", "correct_answer": 62, "events": [["submit", 2458965]], "time_left_end": "67", "answered_time": 2458965, "user_answer": "62", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "67", "question_time_start": 2458965, "question": "4+3+37", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 2462481]], "time_left_end": "64", "answered_time": 2462481, "user_answer": "44", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "64", "question_time_start": 2462482, "question": "6+98+19", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["calc_1", 2484103], ["calc_0", 2484716], ["calc_4", 2485224], ["calc_+", 2485781], ["calc_1", 2486449], ["calc_9", 2486949], ["calc_=", 2487740], ["submit", 2491231]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "35", "answered_time": 2491230, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "35", "question_time_start": 2491231, "question": "3+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 112, "events": [["submit", 2509723]], "time_left_end": "17", "answered_time": 2509723, "user_answer": "112", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "17", "question_time_start": 2509724, "question": "13+57", "correct_answer": 70, "events": [["submit", 2513785]], "time_left_end": "12", "answered_time": 2513785, "user_answer": "70", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "12", "question_time_start": 2513786, "question": "3+18+89", "correct_answer": 110, "events": [["submit", 2521009]], "time_left_end": "5", "answered_time": 2521009, "user_answer": "110", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "5", "question_time_start": 2521009, "question": "76+727", "correct_answer": 803, "events": []}}}}}